

PHAISAN

KANCHANASUTIRUK

DATA MANAGEMENT

PROFESSIONAL

PROFILE

A Passionate Data Management Professional with 10 + years of experience in analytical data processing area, strong analytical skill, and extensive background in services management. Expertise in SQL, SAS, Python and R with self-taught skill of Cloud Technology (MS Azure)

CONTACT

phaisank@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/phaisan

Mobile: 089 775 6399

Address: 89/116 Moo 8

Saothonghin Bangyai Nonthaburi

11140

EDUCATION

M.Sc / INFORMATION SCIENCE KMITL 1999-2002

M.Sc / MECHANICAL ENGINEERING KASERTSART UNIVERSITY 1994-1998

EXPERIENCE

AVP, DATA MANAGEMENT, CIMB THAI BANK PCL.

NOV 2018 - PRESENT

- Explore, organize, and manipulate data across bank data source systems to develops data mart infrastructure
- Develops and drives multiple data-driven analytical projects in Consumer Banking and Risk Management
- Mentor MIS Team for technical architecture matters

AVP, ANALYTICS SUPPORT, UNITED OVERSEAS BANK (THAI) PCL.

APR 2015 - OCT 2018

- Monitoring and maintaining an existing Retail Data Mart Infrastructure
- Analysis, Design and Implementing data mart enhancement covering portfolio management, marketing performance tracking as well as strategic planning
- Maintaining the data preparation and execution of Marketing Campaign Processes
- Support Special Projects for Data Integration matters
- Consolidating existing SAS Program to develop automated data processing
- Support Ad hoc Data Inquiry/Analysis Request to support business decision making

SERVICES DELIVERY MANAGER, ORACLE CORPORATION (THAILAND)

2011 - 2015

- Single Point of Contact, responsible for post sales supports management of Oracle's customer.
- Share Oracle's best practices and provide proactive and reactive situation management to help maximize the value of customer's investment in Oracle Products.
- Recommendation and Implementation of Oracle's support processes and tools.
- Plan and coordinate the delivery of Advanced Customer Services Program with Customer and Oracle's Service Delivery Engineer.
- Working across Lines of Business in Oracle to develop Account Plans, making sure The Customer's strategies and Goals are aligned with Oracle Initiatives.

CERTIFICATIONS

Microsoft Certified

Azure Fundamental
Azure Data Fundamental
Azure Al Fundamental

SAS Hadoop Data Management

KEY SKILLS

- Database: MS SQL Server, Oracle
- Programming: SQL, SAS, R, Python
- Visualized Tool: MS Power BI, Tableau
- Cloud: MS Azure

DATABASE OPERATION TEAM LEADER, WUNDERMAN (THAILAND)

2011

- Lead team for supporting data-driven marketing activities across ASEAN markets for a major global client
- Administration of Oracle CRM On-Demand Application
- Manage weekly discussion with the team across countries

BUSINESS INTELLIGENCE CONSULTANT, LAWSON SOFTWARE (THAILAND)

2008 - 2011

- Providing Consultation for Lawson Software's BI Solution
- Gathering business requirement for reporting and data integration matters
- Data Mart Design & Implementation based on Microsoft BI Solution
- Install and configure relevant software components
- Assistance for Pre-sales activities relevant to the solution.
- Support Client for troubleshooting and maintenance issues

TECHNICAL CONSULTANT-DATA MANAGEMENT, INTERNATIONAL RESEARCH CORPORATION PCL.

2005 - 2008

- BI solution Implementation based on SAS BI Solution
- Data Warehouse Project Implementation (Design, Development and Test)
- Involving in Project Selling from start to finish which including:
 - Assess customer requirement and propose an effective solution through the product presentation, demonstration as well as the prove of concept
 - o Response for the relevant customer's RFIs, RFQs and RFPs Processes

SALES CONSULTANT, EXTREME SYSTEM CO., LTD.

2003 - 2005

Acquire new customers for the software development project